NYSUT Audio-Visual Materials 6174 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Ray Skuse; Dan Sanders, 18 (Box 16)
  Tape 2
- The NYSUT Long-Term Care Plan, 1 (Box 17)
  Produced by Metropolitan Walter Dann Introduction - Done in his office utilizing a teleprompter; Original footage belongs to Metropolitan
- 1997 NYSUT RA Highlights, 2 (Box 17)
- New York Learning Teleconference, 3 (Box 17)
  PBS Special -- A WMHT TV17 broadcast of this program, which is the first in a series of programs, dealing with how New York learns. This video looks at the middle years in school.
- 1997 NYSUT RA Training, 4 (Box 17)
- 1997 NYSUT RA Training, 5 (Box 17)
- Capital Region Educational Profile -- Schnurr and Jackson, 6 (Box 17)
- People for the American Way; Public Schools under attack, 7 (Box 17)
  December 1986
- Schnurr and Jackson -- New York: the State of Education, 8 (Box 17)
- Protect Yourself -- It's your job, I's your body, 1991; 9 (Box 17)
  with O.J. Simpson, A.I.S. produced -- 3/10/1991
- Learning in New York Teleconference, 1987; 10 (Box 17)
  November 10, 1987
- NYSUT - February 1986 -- Teaching children to think, ESIPA, U.S.S.R., 11 (Box 17)
- Controversy in the classroom, 12 (Box 17)
- Children at risk, 13 (Box 17)
  NYSUT produced -- this segment is used to promo the Children At Risk Workshop conducted by NYSUT's Research and Educ. Svcs.
- The Imagination Celebration, 14 (Box 17)
- Crisis in Urban Education -- Schnurr and Jackson, 15 (Box 17)
  tape #60-008
- NYSUT - SRP Conference - 3/11/1989, 1 (Box 18)
- Stillwater Rally, Picketing, Board Meeting, 2 (Box 18)
  904-03
- Stillwater Rally -- Rally, Speeches, interviews -- 1/24/1989, 3 (Box 18)
- Stillwater Rally -- Board Meeting -- Rally, 4 (Box 18)
  904-04
- Grandville Rally -- Superintendent interview, 5 (Box 18)
- Grandville Rally -- Speeches, 6 (Box 18)
- Grandville Rally -- Interviews, 7 (Box 18)
- NYSUT: Financial Foundations Introduction, 1994; 8 (Box 18)
  Video from local Presidents' -- mailing -- August 12, 1994
- Focus on education cooperative learning -- Robert Sladen, 1988; 9 (Box 18)
  January, 1988
- S.R.P. Conf. - Keynote Address by Toni Cortese, 1988; 10 (Box 18)
  11-8-1988
- Address of Governor Mario Cuomo to the 1987 NYSUT Representative Assembly, 11 (Box 18)
- Tenure: Setting the record straight, 12 (Box 18)
  NYSUT
- Tenure: Setting the record straight, 13 (Box 18)
- Tenure: Setting the record straight, 14 (Box 18)
- How your union can help you: in your early years of teaching, 15 (Box 18)
  United Federation of Teachers -- includes booklet
- All in favor (Box 19)
  - All in Favor, 1 (Box 19)
    motion picture (3 reels)
- Waldenville I (Box 20)
  - Waldenville I, 1 (Box 20)
    motion picture - case and movie damaged
- Waldenville II (Box 21)
  - Waldenville II, 1 (Box 21)
    motion picture -
- Dimensions of Bargaining (Box 22)
  - Dimensions of Bargaining, 1 (Box 22)
    motion picture - film box damaged, not sure about condition of movie
- H2 O Town B.O.E. Meeting -- 11/11/1988, 1 (Box 23)
  removed from 6174/004, box 27, f17; North Country Correspondence
- Board Meeting (original) -- 11/11/1988, 2 (Box 23)
- Unlabeled, 3 (Box 23)
- Milestones in Mentoring, 4 (Box 23)
- Diversity in Mentoring, 5 (Box 23)
- American Federation of Teachers - Building on the past for a better future, 6 (Box 23)
- Focus on Education - AIDS Education in the Classroom, 1987; 7 (Box 23)
  February 1987
- American Federation of Teachers - AFT Quest 1987, 8 (Box 23)
  Classroom Strategies for Aids Education /Steve Sroka
- Button, Button (Box 24)
  - Button, Button, 1 (Box 24)
- Harmonics of Conflict (Box 25)
  - Harmonics of conflict, 1 (Box 25)
- AFT: A union of teachers (Box 26)
  - AFT: a union of teachers, 1 (Box 26)
- Am-Bush at the White House, 1 (Box 27)
  American Federation of Teachers
- South Africa - Johannesburg - Kwazulu - Grahamstown - Capetown, 1 (Box 28)
- Strategy Meeting -- Lawton Letters -- Schmidt recommendations, 1 (Box 29)
- Capetown, 1 (Box 30)
- Zimbabwe -- South Africa -- Johannesburg, 1 (Box 31)